Si Qi
You're grown up now, time to get married.
Dad, it's your birthday today.
Why are you saying that?
Come on, Dad. Let's buy a strawberry cake.
It's a limited edition.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Isn't this my future father-in-law?
What's going on between you two?
Just guys being guys.
Let it go unsaid.
Sheng Yuanzhou, you...
You and Si Qi have an engagement!
How can you...
mess around with some outsider?
And...
I know.
Dad, Dad!
Sheng Yuanzhou, it's my dad's birthday today.
Can you tone it down a bit?
We're not even married yet.
He's not my father-in-law yet, either.
What, you want me to wish him a happy birthday?
If I don't have some fun while I still can,
then after we get married,
I won't be able to do it this openly, right?
You're shameless.
A rich Young Master like me...
Do you really want me to...
tie myself to one woman forever?
If you can't even handle that,
you still want to marry into the Sheng family?
Sheng Yuanzhou, I'm telling you.
I'm not interested in you or the Sheng family.
You called me here on purpose
just to watch you get slapped?
Take care, father-in-law.
Why did you intentionally make them think
that you got a room with another woman?
If you want to end your engagement to Lin Si Qi,
letting her dad see it with his own eyes
what a player I am
isn't that more direct?
Old foxes like them
don't care how messy your private life is.
They only care whether you've got money.
Besides,
the Lin Family hospital is still waiting on
Prosperity Group's money to save it.
If you really want to break it off with Lin Si Qi,
it's actually pretty simple.
Everyone in our circle knows
Lin Si Qi fell for a poor guy.
With you being such a huge cuckold,
isn't that enough to be
a reason for you to end the engagement?
Since they love the Sheng family's money,
they won't end the engagement easily.
Yeah, true.
Who'd drop a golden goose like the Shengs?
If you really
want to dump that girl Lin Si Qi,
why don't you consider
a marriage alliance with me?
I'm much more mature than Lin Si Qi,
that naive little girl.
I know how the world works.
When I look at a woman,
I don't think with my dick.
You look at her brains,
and her money power.
Women you can sleep with are everywhere.
Women who can make money?
Not many.
Prosperity Group's eldest son
actually cares if a woman can make money?
As you know,
Prosperity Group is still run by my dad.
I don't want to be a figurehead heir.
So...
Got any good ways to make money?
Interesting.
You're not like those lousy men.
You think differently.
Ever heard of Hades Club?
Hades Club?
I'm not like Zhu Zipeng, that idiot
who only knows how to play with women.
I'm like you.
Money comes first.
So you started Hades Club.
I don't have that kind of pull.
I just provide them
a place to gather.
I make introductions and connections,
and earn a little for my trouble.
Anyone who can get into Hades Club
is a top-tier tycoon in this country.
Any industry, any field.
All across the nation.
The only requirement is money.
After all, you must be on the same level
to play together.
So,
they're all doing business.
You're something else.
When people come to my place,
it's just to have a few drinks,
make some friends,
talk about global economic trends,
and see what opportunities are out there.
Have you heard of the Pareto principle?
Of course.
It's the same in the wealth world.
Jewish people make up
0.2 percent of the world's population,
yet they hold
80 percent of the world's wealth.
Hades has its own Pareto principle too.
Hades members
are 0.02% of the nation's population.
That 0.02%
is like the Jewish people.
See those two over there?
The one in the black suit jacket
is the founder of Great Qin Capital.
The one who just turned and greeted us
is Xiao Hang, Shipping Magnate of the East.
They're the real titans of business.
Come. I'll introduce you to new friends.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Let me introduce a new friend.
Prosperity Group's Young Master.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Welcome, welcome, welcome, brother.
Come, come.
Hello, hello.
What you were just saying...
about Dongbao Steel's restructuring,
is it true or not?
True or not?
We'll know once the market news drops.
Make sure you seize the chance.
Rich people really do make money so easily
Not like...
...me. I lost it all.
It can jump 20 percent in a single day.
What a shame.
I just don't have enough capital.
Mr. Sheng.
What do you need such a huge sum for?
You don't need to ask so much.
But...
Chairman Sheng won't allow you...
...to use company funds whenever you want.
In your personal account,
you get 150,000 a month as spending money.
And you spend it all every month.
This month,
you paid for Zhang Xiaobei's family's...
...100,000 in medical bills.
Right now, in the account,
there's only 50,000 left.
So I don't have...
...any other personal assets?
Every time you use money,
you need Chairman Sheng's approval.
If I could invest a few million more...
Then when I go back to my parents,
they won't have to worry about money.
But where am I supposed to get more money?
Borrow it.
Yeah.
A while back, didn't I make my dad...
...mad?
So he froze my card.
I figured, with news about Dongbao Steel...
...this good,
I couldn't just let it go to waste.
Prosperity Group's Young Master borrows?
Even if you don't have cash on hand,
you've still got assets.
Assets? What assets?
That land your mom left you.
It's zoned into the Free Trade Zone now.
It must be worth hundreds of millions.
Sell it,
and you'll have money.
Land...
Sheng Yuanzhou's mom left him...
...that huge a piece of land?
If he sells it,
it's easily over a hundred million.
Back then, why did his mom...
...buy such a huge stretch of wasteland?
Are you...
Young Master?
It's me.
Granny Shen, who chased you to feed you.
Granny Shen...
I'm old, you don't recognize me anymore.
How could I not recognize you?
Look how gloomy it is.
And it's drizzling, too.
I just couldn't see you clearly.
You sneaked out to see your mom again.
Come this way.
Didn't Sheng Yuanzhou's mom pass away?
Take a quick look and hurry back.
If your father finds out, he'll be mad.
I said it before.
Without my permission,
no one is allowed to go there.
Sneaking over there...
What were you trying to do?
But...
That's my mom!
Shut up.
You forgot the rules again, didn't you?
In this family, you must not mention her.
Let me tell you.
In this house, you don't get to do...
...whatever you feel like.
Today, you're going to kneel right here.
And reflect on it properly.
All I did was visit my mother's grave.
Was that really worth such a huge tantrum?
No...
Something's off. There's always a reason.
I haven't had Granny Shen's food in ages.
Little Young Master.
Why are you here again?
All these years,
you've been watching this place alone.
I wanted to keep you company.
No, no.
Hurry back.
Didn't your dad punish you yesterday?
And you still came after that?
This is my mom's grave.
Why can't I come?
Every time,
I see that flower bed up front,
I remember Madam, taking you as a kid...
...to plant flowers.
This place...
It's full of memories of you two.
Madam...
Look at the Young Master.
He misses you so much.
How could you be so heartless?
You just left him behind and walked away.
Your father won't let you come.
So don't go against him.
If he punishes you,
Madam will be upset.
Where Sheng Yuanzhou grew up...
Why won't Sheng Shizhong let him come back?
That's because my dad is unreasonable.
I'm not scared of him.
But you can't blame him for all of it.
After all, your mom betrayed him first.
Betrayed?
Sheng Yuanzhou's mother...
She cheated.
Granny Shen.
What really happened back then?
Those awful things...
Shouldn't be remembered.
Granny Shen, please tell me.
I'm grown up now.
I have the right to know.
No one will tell me.
Only you can.
You're the only one who remembers her,
The only one who still talks about her.
Only you can tell me about her.
You don't want, in a few more years,
For me to forget even my mom, do you?
All right.
Then I'll tell you about her.
Truth is, your parents loved each other.
They were childhood sweethearts after all.
After you were born,
They were even closer than most couples.
But somehow,
Your mom suddenly...
Fell for the family driver, Hu Jin.
She made a fuss every day to go see him.
Crying and causing scenes.
The family couldn't stop her at all.
Madam!
Later...
After that driver left,
Your mom took her own life.
So...
Sheng Shizhong doesn't want to bring up
being a cuckold.
That's why he won't let anyone set foot in
Sheng Yuanzhou's mother's grave site.
Now...
You understand your father's pain, right?
Mr. Sheng.
It's time. You should go.
Go where?
Today is your appointment with Dr. Chen.
Dr. Chen...
I forgot.
Let's go.
How have you been feeling lately?
Same as always.
Are you still taking your meds on time?
Meds...
Do you still keep having that nightmare?
Sheng Yuanzhou...
You've got quite a few secrets.
Dr. Chen.
Do you still remember, when I was little,
The first time you met me,
What I was like?
You were eight then.
Very quiet.
Very sweet.
You loved drawing.
Do you still have my drawings?
Of course.
I want to see them.
Lately I miss those childhood days.
I miss who you were back then, too.
So little.
You always sat there quietly,
Drawing the world as you saw it.
From your pictures,
I could tell you had a
Warm, gentle heart.
You have eyes to see the world's beauty.